articlelocker.com 2013-08-06

# ArticleLocker.com - FREE Articles for Your Website, Ezine or Blog

**Introduction**  
ArticleLocker.com respects each individual’s right to personal privacy.  We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement.  This statement applies solely to information collected at ArticleLocker.com’s Web site. ****

**Part I.   Information Collection**   
ArticleLocker.com collects information through our Web site at several points.  We collect the following information about primary visitors: Name, Street Address, City, State/Province, Zip Code, Country, Telephone Numbers, E-mail addresses. 

We may also collect certain types of personally identifiable information which our users divulge about other people, such as referrals, gift purchases or other situations. ArticleLocker.com does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information. 

We collect the following general data that is not personally identifiable information: country or province, zip code and state.  We collect demographic data in order to better serve our clients. 

We verify the accuracy of this information by validating via email addresses. 

We collect this information through methods such as registration forms, email communications and so on.  Describe what information is collected through each method].  The information is collected voluntarily.   To receive our services, your address is mandatory because we sometimes need to send funds to clients via our affiliate program.  Other information we request is optional. 

We do employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable ArticleLocker.com to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users.  Our cookies do have an expiration date. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. 

**No** third parties collect any information from our Web site or user database. 

**Part II.   Information Usage.   
**The information collected by ArticleLocker.com will be used for strictly internal purposes only.  Users who provide information will receive email announcements or advertisements pertaining only to our services. 

Registered users may receive additional announcements from us about products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. 

The information we collect will not be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history.  We will not supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources such as credit history to authorize purchases. 

We may share data with the following third parties: PayPal, ClickBank or other third party payment services that are necessary to carry out a transaction.  These third parties will use the information only for a transaction between you and ArticleLocker.com.  We offer links to other Web sites.  Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies.  Their standards may differ from ours. 

Our Web site offers chats, forums or message boards.  Please be advised that information posted in these venues becomes public knowledge. 

If our policy on information collection or uses changes, will advise you by email within 1 week of modification. 

**Part III.   Access to Information   
**ArticleLocker.com maintains the accuracy of our information by cross-checking our own databases and validating email addresses.  Users may access their own personal information and contact us about inaccuracies they may find.  Log in to your account management control panel to do so.  Users may delete their information from our database by contacting [support@articlelocker.com](mailto:support@articlelocker.com). 

**Part IV. Problem Resolution  
**If problems arise, users may contact ArticleLocker.com via email at: [support@articlelocker.com](mailto:support@articlelocker.com).  We are committed to resolving disputes within a reasonable time frame.

**Part V. Data Storage and Security  
**ArticleLocker.com protects user information with the following security measures: security protocols, secure servers, firewalls, SSL encryption and other technology and procedures used to protect consumer privacy. 

If you have any further questions about privacy or security, please contact us by sending an email to: [info@articlelocker.com](mailto:info@articlelocker.com).
